webleaguemanager.com 2009-12-27

# Fantasy Insights <:> Pricacy Policy

### Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:

    Our Commitment To Privacy
    The Information We Collect
    How We Use Information
    Our Commitment To Data Security
    Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
    How To Correct Your Information
    How To Contact Us

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

We also participate in the Council of Better Business Bureaus' BBB _OnLine®_ Privacy Program, and comply with all the BBB _OnLine_ privacy standards. Further information about this program is available at [http://www.bbbonline.org.](http://www.bbbonline.org/)

### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the fantasyinsights.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

    Name 
    Address 
    Email address 
    Phone number 
    Credit/Debit Card Information 

### The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that _X_ number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that _Y_ number of men and _Z_ number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

### How You Can Correct Your Information

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [support@fantasyinsights.com](mailto:support@fantasyinsights.com)
